[
    {
        "title": "Analyzed Article",
        "Contains_Propaganda": "Yes",
        "Avg_Confidence": 0.999755064646403,
        "Confidence_Label": "High Confidence",
        "Detailed_Propaganda": {},
        "Sentiment": {
            "label": "Negative",
            "score": 0.29337334632873535
        },
        "Entities": [
            [
                "British",
                "NORP"
            ],
            [
                "American",
                "NORP"
            ],
            [
                "Andrew Tate",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Romania",
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "more than seven months",
                "DATE"
            ],
            [
                "August 2023",
                "DATE"
            ],
            [
                "Tristan",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "two",
                "CARDINAL"
            ],
            [
                "UK",
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "Andrew Tate",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "British",
                "NORP"
            ],
            [
                "2016",
                "DATE"
            ],
            [
                "six days",
                "DATE"
            ],
            [
                "36-year-old",
                "DATE"
            ],
            [
                "more than 6.9 million",
                "CARDINAL"
            ],
            [
                "Andrew Tate",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Andrew Tate '",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Andrew Tate",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "BBC",
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                "Andrew Tate",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Tate",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Emory Andrew Tate - was",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "December 1986",
                "DATE"
            ],
            [
                "American",
                "NORP"
            ],
            [
                "the US Air Force",
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                "Britain",
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "UK",
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "America",
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "Tate",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Tate",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Luton",
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "England",
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "Tate",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Tristan",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "England",
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "KFC",
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                "Tate",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "four",
                "CARDINAL"
            ],
            [
                "Tate",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "December 2022",
                "DATE"
            ],
            [
                "Greta Thunberg",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "33",
                "CARDINAL"
            ],
            [
                "TikTok",
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                "AndrewTate",
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                "billions",
                "CARDINAL"
            ]
        ],
        "Bias_Terms_Found": [
            "controversial",
            "allegations"
        ],
        "final_score": 0,
        "Timestamp": "2024-12-18T02:14:06.160429",
        "Username": "",
        "Email": ""
    },
    {
        "title": "Analyzed Article",
        "Contains_Propaganda": "Yes",
        "Avg_Confidence": 0.9998567163944244,
        "Confidence_Label": "High Confidence",
        "Detailed_Propaganda": {
            "Appeals to Authority": [
                [
                    "The self-proclaimed misogynist influencer Published 23 July Share close panel Share page Copy link About sharing Image source, Channel 5 Image caption, Andrew Tate was removed from Big Brother over a video that appeared to show him assault a woman The controversial British-American influencer Andrew Tate is facing trial in Romania.",
                    